

chueyangib@gmail.com 414-469-3284

SUMMARY

Currently working on a certificate in Full Stack Development at the University of Minnesota with skills in CSS, JavaScript, and Node. Previously, worked in operations manager positions and fell in love with tech and rapid prototyping leading to current pursuit of Full Stack Development as a career.

EXPERIENCES

Blackbaud, St. Paul, MN

Temp-to-Hire, Robert Half Office Team, MN *Office Manager*

Feb 2020 – present Jul 2019 – Feb 2020

- Along with managing the daily operations at a software company, serve as the Executive Assistant to two senior level executives with responsibilities of coordinating schedules, reconciling expense reports, arranging travel, and executing on-site and off-site meetings.
- Achievements include executing over 70+ catering events, overseeing a kitchen and branding renovation, new vendor purchases (printers and coffee vendors), designing certificates for clients who are in the top percentage of institutional fundraisers.
- Spearhead the culture club to create an engaging and interactive environment. Create, organize and execute weekly events: volunteering, food competitions, educational, pot-lucks, and holiday parties.

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

CoMotion MakerSpace Manager

Dec 2015 – Mar 2019

- Led the effective management and execution of multiple makerspace projects, including: a \$220K space renovation and woodshop expansion, multiple grants totaling over \$400K that included the set-up of a tool lending library and an augmented reality program, over five Seattle Library and low-income community makerspace pop-ups; and organized events and summits drawing over 1500 individuals.
- Managed and streamlined budget, procurement, and reconciliation processes for \$200K annual budget.
- Engaged with varied stakeholders (students, professors, and high-level university officials) to ensure alignment with the University mission, effective delivery of services, compliance, and promote innovation and entrepreneurship. Examples include working with: the Environmental Health & Safety department to implement shop safety policies and audits; Risk Management Office and the Attorney General's Office to review policies and liabilities; Safety Committee Group to share best practices; Admissions Office, Resource Center, and Buerk Center to promote innovation and entrepreneurship.
- Developed and improved policies and procedures, including: membership eligibility, safety trainings, standard operating procedures for equipment; developed an operations manual; shop audits processes.
- Hired, trained, and supervised 10 staff, 30 mentors, and a handful of interns. Advised students on best practices with design, rapid prototyping techniques and equipment use.
- Developed and implemented curricula, including: identifying stakeholder needs, developing content and learning tools, as well as developing diagnostic and evaluation methods.
- Other responsibilities facilities management, space planning, equipment maintenance, marketing, outreach, website and social media.

Community-University Health Care Center, University of Minnesota, MN Nov 2012 - Dec 2013 Administrative Specialist

- Supported renovation project with signification communications, including web content development, and managed the phone systems bids and implementation of over 150 new phones at the clinic.
- Supported multiple clinic grants, initiatives and audits: program-reporting, proposal, and grant initiatives, and ensured agreements and contracts are consistent with university and contracted agency policies.

Cambridge University, Cambridge, UK

Jun 2011 - Jun 2012

Temporary Employment Services

- Graduate Admissions Office: Made conditional admission offers to applicants for graduate study, which required specialized knowledge of Cambridge University's minimum requirements and international equivalencies. Advised students on application processes, housing and other queries.
- Research Operations Office: Managed principal investigators' (PI) proposals, contracts, grants, and billings. Responsibilities included opening and closing grants; modifying grants and budgets; preparing invoices; reconciling foreign exchange rates for loss or gains; and quality assurance on grant processes.

Advanced Engineering Associates International, Inc., Washington, D.C. Feb 2008 - Oct 2010 Senior Office Administrator

- Led documentation tasks and coordinated activities related to technical expert recruitment and qualification, status tracking, and communications with candidates for proposals. Participated in the company's numerous proposal teams, including for various successful bids submitted to bilateral and multilateral organizations.
- Managed the home office support the US\$5.4 million, The Georgia "Energy Capacity Initiative (ECI)" and the Kosovo "Assistance to the Privatization of the Distribution System" Projects. Provided backstopping support, such as research, travel arrangements, obtained country clearances and visas for U.S. expatriates and project contractor personnel, and provided status updates to all involved parties.
- As Travel Coordinator for the USTDA "Pakistan: Bagasse-based Cogeneration Development OV," drafted formal correspondence for delegates on travel and other requirements, provided timely information and options for visas and flights, and arranged all staff and delegate air and ground transportation needs, lodging, meals, meeting facilities, photography and insurance.

National Coalition for Asian Pacific American Community Development, D.C. May 2006 - Feb 2008 Administrative Associate

- Responsible for overall administrative and office management, supporting the financial operation, creating policies and procedures for the organization's database, listsery, and contracts and inventory.
- Assisted in planning and executing the organization's 2007 annual convention in Hawaii, which brought in speakers and more than 1000 coalition members from all over the country.
- Provided significant communications and administrative support, as the Public Policy Intern (summer 2006), for the Save New Orleans East coalition efforts, wrote fact sheets and informational materials on the Asian American Pacific Islander Serving Institutions bill, and conducted research on the Community Reinvestment Act.

Outdoor Education Program, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C. Logistics Manager/Georgetown Outdoor Adventure Trainer (GOAT) Jan 2004 - May 2008

• Developed and planned outdoor education curriculum; taught and trained guides on all aspects of leading outdoor programs, including logistics, planning, leading, and managing and minimizing risks in the outdoors, and evaluating trips. Trips include rock climbing, camping, hiking, biking, and kayaking.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Web Development, University of Minnesota, MN Bachelor of Arts in English, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.

3/2020-present 2007